

FULLSTACK .NET DEVELOPER

#### **Details**

Stockholm

Sweden

+4670 293 67 58

timhanssonmeng@gmail.com

#### Links

**GitHub** 

LinkedIn

SoundCloud

#### **Skills**

**Problem Solving** 

Ability to Work in a Team

**Communication Skills** 

Creativity

Stress Resistance

## Languages

Swedish

English

Chinese

Norwegian

German

French

# Hobbies

Cooking, video games, hiking/camping & music.

## Resume

Motivated and enthusiastic person with extensive experience in various industries. Extremely quick learner and with brilliant collaboration skills. Willing to work hard to achieve the best possible results with a high ability to focus. Prioritises good communication and teamwork.

## Aim

Wish to combine my logical skills with my creative ability in software development. Looking for a role with even greater responsibility in the future.

# **Work History**

#### Professional Musician, Stavanger Symphony Orchestra, Stavanger

AUGUST 2017 - DECEMBER 2022

- Worked in a team and collaborated with pop artists, songwriters and composers.
- Led the party committee that organised festivities and team building events for all 98 employees.
- Volunteered for regularly playing music in worldwide broadcast live streams during the Covid-19 pandemic.
- Was part of the orchestra's culture team that was responsible for constantly improving the daily work environment.
- Attended regular workshops to develop as a musician.
- Travelled around Norway and arranged concerts for various companies.

#### Personal Trainer, Self Employed, Hybrid

FEBRUARY 2021 - JUNE 2022

- Coached both on site and online.
- Made sure customers always felt comfortable and treated with respect.
- Built individual training programs for each client's specific goals and needs.
- Offered rehab training for clients with injuries or physical pain.
- Planned and designed nutrition and diet programs for each client.

#### Manager/Bartender, SSO Bar, Stavanger

AUGUST 2018 - DECEMBER 2022

- Had responsibility for all purchases and logistics.
- Was partly responsible for finances and management planning.
- Greeted all customers with positive energy and served a variety of beverages.
- Responsible for interior design and decor.
- Responsible for technical maintenance and cleaning of equipment.

### Education

## Fullstack .NET Web Developer, Chas Academy, Stockholm

SEPTEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

## **EHFA-Certified Personal Trainer, AFPT, Stavanger**

SEPTEMBER 2020 - FEBRUARY 2021

### Master of Arts, Guildhall School of Music & Drama, London

SEPTEMBER 2015 - JULY 2017

## Bachelor of Arts, Sibelius Academy, Helsinki

AUGUST 2012 - JUNE 2015